Ajay
in the comment box,
hello, hello guys,
good evening, welcome all of you to the
Fabric Cotton to Running series, and
through this team, we will talk
about the results of the looting quarter.
Here, the company has just released its
results, and as I
tell you, you will see all the results on this channel,
and my goal is to
share the results with you first. So, you can see that
this time the company has issued an interim dividend of four rupees
for its investors,
whose record date is November 1, 2021,
which means that if you keep this topic in your portfolio
till November 1, 2021, then you will be
eligible for this interim dividend, and
its payment is on November 19, 2021. Now let's
go directly to the results and see
what kind of results the company has posted here.
I will enlarge the screen for you all
so that you can
see it all alone here, so you can see where
whatever is there here is in lakhs, so I will tell
you.  I will convert it into crores and explain it to you so that
you can understand it and I can
also explain it in the same way. So you can see that the
total income of the company
in the September quarter was Rs. 3808 crores. The
total income of the company in the June quarter was Rs.
3800.31 crores. So you can see
that there is no change in the income on a quarter-on-quarter basis.
If we talk about
share on air basis, then you can see that there is a
very good growth in the income here
because
last year in the same quarter the
total income of the company was Rs. 2883 crores. So there is
growth in income on air basis
but there is no change on a quarterly basis.
Now if we talk about expenses, here on a
quarterly basis the company's
expenses have reduced but on shares the
company's expenses are big.
Now let's talk about profit for tax.
You can see that in profit for tax,
petrol quarterly  On the basis, very good
growth is seen and the share and A
specific can be seen, you
can see that in the June quarter, the
profit of the company was 258
crores and in the September quarter of Current Affairs, the
profit profit there was
approximately 594 crores and if we talk about the
last same quarter, then the
profit in the last same quarter would have been 554 crores,
so you can see that on the air base and
cotton quarter basis,
we are seeing mutual growth in the profit act here,
now let's talk about the net profit,
you can see that in the net profit, there is a
very strong difference on the tomo face
because
in the June quarter, the net profit of the company is
194 crores, whereas in the September quarter of Current Affairs, the
net profit of the company is 446 crores, so the
company has performed very well here,
but on tomo basis and if we talk on year
basis, then you can see that
in the last year SIM quarter  The
net profit of this company is 24 to 15 crores
here and on which growth is seen in net profit.
Now let's talk about
GPS, you can see that
here we are seeing tremendous growth on a quarterly basis.
Where the GPS in the June quarter was 3.6, the
GPS of the current year in the September quarter is 9.11 and you can see
that the GPS in the same quarter last year was
9.15. So, there is a
further decline in space here on a
yearly basis, but a very impressive jump is being
seen here on a quarterly basis. So the
performance of the company here
and on a yearly basis has been decent. There is
growth in very good gifts.
Growth is seen in income,
but the performance of the company on a quarterly basis has been
very tremendous.
Now let's take a look at
what kind of action has been seen in the stock today.
So you can see that the
price of the stock today is point one.
With a decline of 1500%, the recipe
closed at
₹1500. The current trend is
also on 3G phones.
You can see that the signal from there is
negative. 35 is running. If we
talk about MS Word, the signal in Remedy
is also negative. But the best
thing you can see here is that the
histogram in MCD, you can see it gradually getting
smaller. The
signal is this center line. The
way the company has posted the results here, it may
break the center line and move upwards.
This program is closing small. It is
possible that in tomorrow's days,
this program may be seen moving upwards.
I have been saying continuously that by
buying the insurance sector, hence the last time the
results of A Proof were also out and I still
tell you that you
can keep this stock in your portfolio. In the short term,
this trick will give you very good returns.  You can
talk about the ICC Alam Board.
Starting from this side, there is no shortage of these two stars
and along with that, there is no shortage of good staff as well,
but I am keeping these stocks in focus.
So, subscribe to this channel and
install it. If you want to make profits in the short term, then
you will see good profits
in these good stocks. So,
if you can find it in any way here, then you should do it
and you can do it at the level. There is
a pin here which I will
tell you that if you can
read that the company's Chief Medical
Officer has appointed it, due to which
you can see
that here it is mentioned that there is resignation of Chief
Minister and Compliance Officer, so this is
their design. So if there is any
excuse for the market to come down,
if for any reason there is a day, then you should buy the
stock. Otherwise, the
performance of the company,
both on a total basis and on the stock and air base,
is tremendous. You
can keep this topic in your portfolio. And lastly, we
saw that when  Now, those
partners who have a significant stake here,
I forgot your name. What's the situation now? Okay, so since then,
we've
seen a lot of pressure on the stock when
they consolidated here. But even then,
I was saying that you should try this trick. Those who were
stuck at higher levels,
see it, and by tweeting globally,
you'll see significant long-term
gains. As you can see, as the
company has posted its results here,
you're seeing excellent performance. You're seeing it
in ROI, net profit, and
income. That's why
I'm saying that you can
keep the stock in your portfolio.
I've already told you that the market
needs only one excuse: the resignation of the
Chief Legal and Compliance Officer. Okay,
you can take note of this and move on. Nothing else
here is related to this result.
And Digit, I've already told you
that the company has run out a tweet of Rs 4 here,
and its record
date.  If I'm going to tell you again,
its record date is 19th November 2021. The
current payment is 19th November 2021. Okay, so
if you keep it in your portfolio till 1st November 2021, then
you will be
eligible for this interim dividend. So
these were the results of AC Saver Mode Quarter 2,
which I shared with you here.
I always try to
send you the results as soon as possible. So, I appreciate it so much that I request you to
like, share the video and
subscribe to the channel. In
our ongoing anniversary celebration, if
you want to know the letter digits from any company and
want to be the first to see it, then along with
that subscribe button,
definitely press the bell icon. So, we'll meet
in the next team with the results of pilots of some other company. That's all for now.
Bye, take care.